

Ali Navidi Sari, Iran → +989339668289 2 years of experience ali_navidi24@yahoo.com

Portfolio: alinavidi.dev/

Frontend Developer

A 22-year-old frontend developer and a recent computer (software) engineering graduate, coding since 2018 and with over 2 years of experience in developing websites, Specializes in Next.js, React.js, HTML, CSS and JavaScript. Trying hard to write clean code, higher up the performance and make the user experience better, always seeking to learn new things. Key achievement: Made a social media for songs single-handedly.

Next.js Skills: React.js JavaScript HTML CSS TypeScript Node.js Cypress Express.js MongoDB SEO Git **Bootstrap** Svelte Remix Tailwind

Experience

Restarone Solutions Inc. restarone.com

Sep 2022 to Dec 2022

Frontend Engineer Toronto, Canada

- Implemented websites, mobile applications, and landing pages from concept through deployment for more than 10k users.
- Integrated enhancements into web design to improve user stickiness, smooth functionality, and boost load times; reduced page load time by 70%.
- Translated UX and business requirements into elegant code solutions.
- Tested web-based product functionality and delivered iterations to customers.

Frontend developer Tehran, Iran

Oben Origin co.

Jan 2020 to Nov 2021

- Standardized all output with a new, responsive, mobile-first approach and strategy, leading to more than 1k users.
- Assessed UX and UI designs for technical feasibility.
- Following SEO best practices, increasing website traffic by 40%.
- Made PWA for different websites which increased users by 72%.
- Fixing bugs and testing for usability.
- Creating tools that enhance site interaction regardless of the browser.

Projects

WESTERNAL | Frontend Developer - Backend Developer - Designer

Westernal is a social media based on songs. User can share posts that include part of a song, the whole song or music video with followers and let the music talk!

 ${\it CSS, Java Script, Express, Cypress, Mongo DB, Next. js, Node. js}$

CINEMA | Frontend Developer - Designer

github.com/westernal/Cinema

Cinema is a platform for watching and downloading movies. A user can login and buy subscriptions to watch the latest movies and series and learn more about cinema, actors/actresses and more.

TypeScript, CSS, JavaScript, Next.js

SARTEL | Frontend Developer - Designer

sari-sartel-westernal.vercel.app/ github.com/westernal/sari-sartel

Sartel is a website and PWA selling mobile phones and accessories.

CSS, JavaScript, Next.js

DASHBOARD | Frontend Developer - Designer

 $An admin \, dashboard \, website \, and \, PWA \, built \, with \, Next. js \, and \, Chart. js \, to \, manage \, website \, data \, and \, content.$

JavaScript, CSS, Next.js, Chart.js

Education

Noshiravni University of Technology nit.ac.ir

Bachelor's of Science, Computer Engineering

Oct 2018 to Feb 2023

Publications

Introducing Westernal: A social media based on songs

DEV Community

 $\textcircled{$\scriptsize \textbf{\oplus}$ dev.to/westernal/introducing-westernal-a-social-media-based-on-songs-1pa9}$

Languages

Farsi Native

English Advanced